<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethereum on Mihail&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://mikirov.xyz/tags/ethereum/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethereum on Mihail&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 23:39:49 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mikirov.xyz/tags/ethereum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ProofPlus - Decentralised Prover Protocol</title>
      <link>https://mikirov.xyz/posts/decentralized-prover-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 23:39:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mikirov.xyz/posts/decentralized-prover-market/</guid>
      <description>WHY? Imagine a world where zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs) are accessible to everyone, where the power to generate these proofs is not confined to a few centralized entities but is spread across a vast, decentralized network. ProofPlus exists to make this vision a reality.&#xA;At the heart of ProofPlus is the belief that decentralization breeds innovation and resilience. We started with a simple question: Why should the power to verify complex computations be restricted to a few, when it could be democratized for all?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point precompile for Rollup DA verification</title>
      <link>https://mikirov.xyz/posts/point-precompile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 23:39:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mikirov.xyz/posts/point-precompile/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the landscape of data availability layers (DALs), the optimization of gas costs on the L1 stands as a paramount concern for enhancing operational efficiency. A notable advancement in this pursuit comes with the integration of the newly added EIP4844 point evaluation precompile within data availability networks. This crucial update holds the potential to significantly improve gas costs on Layer 1 (L1) for verification processes, which is particularly advantageous for Rollups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIP7503 Private transfers</title>
      <link>https://mikirov.xyz/posts/eip-7503-private-transfers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:39:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mikirov.xyz/posts/eip-7503-private-transfers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The need for privacy in digital transactions is paramount in today’s digital age, yet most blockchain technologies fall short in offering complete anonymity. Current methods like mixers are often vulnerable to external threats and regulatory scrutiny. Our proposal addresses these challenges by providing a secure, decentralized solution, ensuring privacy for stakeholders including individual users and organizations requiring confidential transactions.&#xA;This document introduces a solution for achieving private transfers using a burn/mint Zero-Knowledge Proof (ZKP) mechanism, addressing the limitations of cryptocurrency mixers like TornadoCash.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
